James H. Madison papers, 1901-2011 C514
Indiana University Archives
- Indiana University, 1968-2011; undated
  - Committees, 1975-2009
    - IU Press Faculty Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 9)
    - IU Press Search Committee, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Jeffrey Gould Tenure Committee, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Liberal Arts and Management Program [LAMP], 2005-2009 (Box 9)
    - Lilly Library Committee, 1990-1996 (Box 9)
    - Limestone Conference, September 8-9, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Maple Leaf Summer Research Historian, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
    - Mathers Museum Advisory Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
    - Mathers Museum, 1988-1989 (Box 9)
    - McNutt Lecture Series, 1986-2003 (Box 9)
    - Medical History Search Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
    - Merger, Reorganization and Elimination Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 9)
    - Midwest Art Exhibit, Art Museum, 1993-1995 (Box 9)
    - Minority Fellowship, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Mort Lowengrub Review Committee, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Nicole Etcheson, 1989-1997 (Box 9)
    - Philanthropy Library Conference, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
    - Policy Committee, College of Arts and Sciences, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - POLIS Review, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
    - Recommendations (Box 9)
      - 1989 (Box 9)
      - 1989-1994 (Box 9)
      - 1994-1996 (Box 9)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 9)
      - 1998 (Box 9)
    - Rhodes-Marshall Scholarship Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
    - Thomas E. Rodgers, 1989-1996 (Box 9)
    - Summer Faculty Fellowship Committee, 1998 (Box 9)
    - Tenure, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Tenure Policy, 1975-1980 (Box 9)
    - US History Search Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 9)
    - Williamson Grievance, 1998-2001 (Box 9)
    - Zip Disk, References, 1993-2000 (Box 9)
- Activities outside Indiana University, 1974-2005; undated
  - 1787: Legacy of Liberty Ball State, University of Southern Indiana, Fall, 1987 (Box 9)
  - 1800 Vincennes, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Always a River video documentary, 1991 (Box 9)
  - American Association for State and Local History (AASLH) (Box 9)
    - On Doing Local History, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Paper, State History, 1984 (Box 9)
  - African Institute Fellows, July 9, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Club, 1996 (Box 9)
  - American Consumer Culture and the War at Home: World War II and Vietnam, 1998 (Box 9)
  - American Institute of the History of Pharmacy (AIHP), 1989 (Box 9)
  - Benton Murals, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Bloomington Restorations Inc., 1993 (Box 9)
  - Brigham Young NEH-AASLH Conference, June 1993 (Box 9)
  - Business History Conference, April 1989 (Box 9)
  - Camp Brosius, July 1985 (Box 9)
  - Clipper Cruise, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Cincinnati Historical Society Exhibition Review, 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - Civil War Monument I, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Civil War Museum Search Committee, 1999 (Box 10)
  - Connor Prairie in 1940s, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Connor Prairie Lecture, September 11, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Connor Prairie Talk, 1993 (Box 10)
  - Connor Prairie I, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Connor Prairie II, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Connor Prairie, 1997 (Box 10)
  - Connor Prairie Board of Directors (Box 10)
    - October 4, 1996 (Box 10)
    - June 17, 1998 (Box 10)
    - December 2, 1998 (Box 10)
    - March 17, 1999 (Box 10)
    - June 16, 1999 (Box 10)
    - September 15, 1999 (Box 10)
  - Constitution - ICH [Institute for Constitutional History], 1986 (Box 10)
  - Constitutional Lecture Comments, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Continuing Education Class, 1987 (Box 10)
  - Contract Archeology, 1990-1993 (Box 10)
  - Cummins, Summer, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Delta Queen Lecture, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Department of History (University of South Dakota) Five Year Review, November 4, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Directory of Faculty and Staff, Earlham College, Earlham School of Religion, Connor Prairie, 1998-1999 (Box 11)
  - Doing History in Indiana: The Generation Before Ours, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Editorial Board Meeting, May 16, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Eli Lilly Lectures, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Eli Lilly: Patron of Midwestern Archeology, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Encyclopedia Authors, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Encyclopedia for Midwestern Culture, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Educational Resources Information Center (ERIC)/ Clearinghouse for Social Studies/Social Science Education (ChESS), 1988-1990 (Box 11)
  - Federalism Lecture, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Gift for Martin and Sally Ridge, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Hoosier Heritage Foundation (GHHF) (Box 11)
    - 1997 (Box 11)
    - 1998, (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Graduate Colloquium, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Greatest Americans of All Time, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Halcyon Years, Minnestra Cultural Center, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich Inc. Textbook, 1983-1991 (Box 11)
  - Historic Monuments and Sites, undated (Box 11)
  - Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania Publications Seminar, April 1978 (Box 11)
  - The Indiana Academy, 1994-1997 (Box 11)
  - Indiana Association of Historians, 1989-1995 (Box 11)
  - Indiana Committee for the Humanities, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
  - Indiana Division Advisory Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - Indiana Historical Marker Program, 2004-2005 (Box 11)
  - Indiana Historical Society Symposium, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Indiana History Curriculum Project, 1985-1987; 2 Folders (Box 12)
  - The Indiana History Project, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Indiana Magazine of History, 1982-1996 (Box 12)
  - Indiana Pioneers: Their Legacy to the 90s, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Indiana State Museums, 1999-2000 (Box 12)
  - Indiana University of Pennsylvania Magazine, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Indiana's Golden Age 1880-1915, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Indiana's Pioneer Heritage and the End of the Twentieth Century, 1995 (Box 12)
  - James Madison Fellows, July 6, 1987; July 5, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Leadership Bloomington, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Lincoln, 1994-1996 (Box 12)
  - Lyles Station, Indiana, 1986-1989 (Box 12)
  - Midwest Archives Conference (Box 12)
    - November 9-11, 1978 (Box 12)
    - November 2-3, 1998 (Box 12)
  - Midwestern Regional History and Culture Series (Box 12)
    - 1985-1986, 3 Folders (Box 12)
    - 1987-1988, 3 Folders (Box 12)
    - 1989-1993, 5 Folders; (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - 1994, 4 Folders (Box 12)
  - Mini-University, 1987-2009 (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous Lectures, 1976-2000; 4 Folders (Box 12a)
  - Monroe County Carnegie Library Project, 1999-2005 (Box 13)
  - National Archives, 1986 (Box 13)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities(NEH) (Box 13)
    - Panel, August 1977 (Box 13)
    - Panel, March 31, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Public Programs, 1978-1979 (Box 13)
  - Newberry Conference, January 1977 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Ordinance (Box 13)
    - Symposium [and the Constitution], 1985-1986 (Box 13)
    - IU Alumni Magazine, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Organization of American Historians (OAH) (Box 13)
    - Panel, April 13, 1986 (Box 13)
    - Program Comparative Histories of the Heartland, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Search, 1992-1993 (Box 13)
    - Search, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Pathways to the Old Northwest, Indiana Historical Society, July 11, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Penn State Seminar, Continuing Education, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Produce for Victory, Smithsonian, 1994-1995 (Box 13)
  - Prospect Hill Spring Tour, May 23, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Public School History Teaching, 1978-1979 (Box 13)
  - R.I.N.G. Hoosier Heritage, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Religion in Indiana Project, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Shawnee Bluffs, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Society of Indiana Archivists, Long Range Planning Committee, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Spring Mill Workshop, 1993-1995 (Box 13)
  - Spring Workshop, Heroes and Villains, May 9, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Social Science History Association (SSHA), New Orleans, 1987 (Box 13)
  - State and Local History Panel -NEH [National Endowment for the Humanities], April 1977 (Box 13)
  - Summer Institute, University of Southern Indiana, 1989-1990 (Box 13)
  - The Teaching Company, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Train Lecture Notes, 1994-1995 (Box 13)
  - Treasures of Indiana video project, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Treasures of the Seine Trip, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Toward a Biography of Eli Lilly, 2002 (Box 13)
  - U.S. - U.S.S.R. Textbook Project, 1985-1987 (Box 13)
  - The Varieties of History: What We Teach Presenting the Past, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Victoria County History Conference, University of London, 2009 (Box 13)
  - Warsaw University Conference, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Wilton Park Conference, 1982 (Box 13)
- Correspondence, 1973-2001; undated (Box 14)
  - Chronological Correspondence (Box 14)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 14)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 14)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 14)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 14)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 14)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 14)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - Indiana Through Tradition and Change, 1979-1981 (Box 14)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 14)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 14)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 14)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 14)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 14)
    - Newberry Library, November-December,1984 (Box 14)
    - 1984-1986 (Box 14)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 14)
    - Photographs, Eli Lilly Book, 1987-1990 (Box 15)
    - 1988 (Box 15)
    - Eli Lilly Biography, 1988-1989 (Box 15)
    - Lilly Revision, 1988 (Box 15)
    - 1989 (Box 15)
    - 1989 (Box 15)
    - Macmillan/McGraw Hill [publisher], Indiana Book, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
    - Lilly Post-Publication, 1989-1997 (Box 15)
    - 1990 (Box 15)
    - 1991 (Box 15)
    - 1992 (Box 15)
    - 1993 (Box 15)
    - 1994 (Box 15)
    - 1995 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous/Annual Report, 1996 (Box 15)
    - 1997/1998 (Box 15)
    - Hiroshima University, 1997-1998 (Box 15)
    - Baker & Daniels, 1998-2000 (Box 15)
    - 1988-2001 (Box 15)
    - undated (Box 15)
  - Alphabetical Correspondence (Box 15)
    - A, 1994-1997 (Box 15)
    - B, 1993-2001 (Box 15)
    - Chair, 1993-1997 (Box 15)
    - C, 1993-2002 (Box 15)
    - D, 1993-1997 (Box 16)
    - E, 1993-1996 (Box 16)
    - F, 1993-2001 (Box 16)
    - G, 1993-1999 (Box 16)
    - H, 1993-2007 (Box 16)
    - I, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Indiana Association of Historians, 1995-1999 (Box 16)
    - J, 1995-1999 (Box 16)
    - Kinsey, 1993-1997 (Box 16)
    - K, 1993-1998 (Box 16)
    - L, 1993-1999 (Box 16)
    - M, 1993-2000 (Box 16)
    - N, 1993-1998 (Box 16)
    - O, 1997-2001 (Box 16)
    - P, 1993-1998 (Box 16)
    - Q, 1997-2001 (Box 16)
    - RUGS Minority Program Review, 1996-1997 (Box 16)
    - R, 1993-2000 (Box 16)
    - S, 1993-2001 (Box 16)
    - SSDC Policy Committee, 1996-1999 (Box 16)
    - T, 1994-1999 (Box 16)
    - V, 1994-1997 (Box 16)
    - W, 1996-2001 (Box 16)
  - Research notecards for Eli Lilly book, undated (Box 17)
  - Restricted Materials (Box 18)
  - Restricted Materials (Box 19)